preview of the next episode
It's in there.
Konon's costume is black, so he won't look good.
It's a little difficult.
It's me, right?
It would be embarrassing to die if I made a mistake. Sign it.
I'm the cool, all-black beauty today.
Here's a rare scene of her signing.
Ah, Hika-san.
Hika is cute.
She's so cute. I'm going to write too.
Hikaru wrote it, so I'll write that one.
Hey, Otten-chan.
Is that right?
It's cute.
It says Hika.
Thank you.
He's so cute.
Sign that one, too.
I'll take care of it.
He's cute.
Thank you for watching.
Oh, kan-yake. Kanyake. Kanyake. Kanyake.
Kanyake. Kanyake. Kan-yake. Kan-yake.
Aji-toriko-tsume.
I'll give you a bath.
I drew an elderly person's handprint on the bath.
I drew an elderly person's handprint.
It's not dirty at all today.
This is how everyone draws.
I think I'll go to Momochan's place now.
He is so serious.
She looks the same. Like this.
He was so serious.
So cute.
By the way, this is me.
You noticed.
It's true. I ate Louie.
At that time, I was wondering why.
What is this? What scene?
Oh, the smart scene.Ah, smart scene.
This is also Momochan's cool version.
A cool version of you guys.
Don't you know what this face is?
He looks like he's not thinking.
The good looking version.
This one is from Lenarme's lineage.
By the way, this is probably the real deal.
I'm sure.
It's true.
This is Kira.
You can tell, can't you?
You're so vague.
I'll write a heart here.
Thank you.
Yay!
Supi!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Supi-suppi-suppi-suppi-suppi-suppi-suppi-suppi-suppi-suppi
Can I draw like this?
It's fine.
Here.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'll draw it for you.
I'm drawing.
Yes, I'm drawing.
I'll let you draw this.
Okay.
Yes, yes.
Yes, sir.
Tomorrow morning is dawn.
If you were here today, you'd have been there by 5:30.
Why? I don't know.
I was looking forward to it too much. I was too enthusiastic.
My hands were too high.
Wow.
That's so high.
I'm scared.
Are you okay?
Are you okay?Are you okay?
Oh, I'm high.
You're really looking at the camera.
I'm actually looking down and holding your hand.
Look at me.
You're so cute.
Is he smiling?
Yes, I am.
Look at this. I'm glad.
He's trying so hard.
He's so cute.
Mashallah.
Cute.
Shall we?
Yeah.
The picture.
Sankisei.
I draw a lot of pictures.
Hello.
Hello, how are you?
Don't make a mistake about the Kanji King.
Well, not the Kanji King.
Ito, you've been hijacked.
I'll take care of it.
I recommend it.
Are you okay?
I've got it.
On your phone.
Aww.
I'm writing.
Yoo-chan is writing, too.
She's writing
She's writing.
He's so cute!
And there are so many gaps.
I'm trying to figure out how to fill them in nicely.
I'm trying to figure out what I want to draw.
Can I have it drawn soon?Can I have it painted quickly?
Yes, you may. I'm sorry. I don't have time.
I'd like to draw that we're going to play a concert in France.
How's that going?
No, I can do it. I can do it.
It's fine. It's fine. It's not too hard, right?
By the way...
I'd like to show you something.
We're going to France, by the way.
You drew this.
I thought...
It's amazing!
Happy Birthday, President Yumiko!
She drew this even though she graduated.
You'd better guess.
If you don't guess, you'll lose.
Oh, this is it.
Held in Paris, France
Japan Key
Rina-san
Cute!
What do you think?
Oh, I haven't put anything on it yet.
Yui-san
How do you like it?
It's good.
It's cute.
You look cute today.
Have you signed it?
Where is it?
It's so cool.
Look at all the music videos.
Go sign another one.
Sign mine.
There.
I like that one.
Now, I want you to give me a little nokugaki.
No mustache, please.